RG 005:032, Office of the Governor: John Davis Lodge (1951-1955)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 3. State Agency Files, 1951-1955
  - Highway Finance Committee Appointed by Gov. Lodge, 2 folders (Box 575)
  - Autotypist Letters Acknowledged “Highway” (Box 575)
  - Highway Program of Federal Gov[ernmen]t (Proposals for President Eisenhower and Recommendations of Governors’ Conference and Council of State Governments) (Box 575)
  - Highway Department (Box 576)
  - Highway Dep[artmen]t (Comm[issione]r G. Albert Hill) (Box 576)
  - Highway Favorable [Letters favorable to the State’s Position Re: the situation in the Town of Fairfield] (Box 576)
  - Highway, 1952; 3 folders; half the box (Box 576)
  - Highway Department (Box 577)
  - Most files pertain to the proposed Greenwich – Killingly (Box 577)
  - Expressway. Includes a binder of photographs entitled (Box 577)
  - “Directly in the Path of the Thruway in Stamford,” Thruway (Box 577)
  - Relocation Council, Another binder pertains to the Connecticut Safety Commission, 1952 April (Box 577)
  - Housing (State Housing Authority): Includes Memorandum to Governor–Elect Lodge from Albert C. Demers marked, “Confidential,” pertaining to the abolition of the State Housing Authority by the March 1950 Special Session. In 1951, the Authority became the H (Box 577)
  - Housing Expeditor, James McI. Henderson, Director (Box 577)
  - Insurance Commissioner (Box 578)
  - Insurance Dep[artmen]t (Box 578)
  - Joint Committee on State Mental Hospitals (Box 578)
  - Labor Dep[artmen]t, 5 folders (Box 578)
  - Laurel Heights [Sanatorium] (Box 578)
  - Legislative Council (Harry H. Lugg, Director) Legislative Commissioner (Robert Wall) (Box 578)
  - Liquor Control Commission, 2 folders (Box 578)
  - Long Lane School (Box 579)
  - Mansfield State Training School, 2 folders (Box 579)
  - Marketing Authority (Conn[ecticut) (Box 579)
  - Mental Health (Box 579)
  - Merritt Parkway Commission, 2 folders (Box 579)
  - Milk Administration (Hammerberg) (Box 579)
  - Motor Vehicles Dep[artmen]t (Box 579)
  - Motor Vehicles Dep[artmen]t (Charles F. Kelley) (Box 579)
  - Mystic Oral School for the Deaf, 2 folders (Box 579)
  - Norwich State Hospital, 4 folders (Box 579)
  - Park and Forest, 2 folders (Box 580)
  - Personnel Department, 3 folders (Box 580)
  - Public Utilities Commission, 3 folders (Box 580)
  - Public Works Dep[artmen]t, 1952 (Box 580)
  - Public Works Dep[artmen]t, 1953 (Box 580)
  - Public Works Dep[artmen]t, 1954 (Box 580)
  - Public Works Dep[artmen]t, 2 folders and unfiled reports (Box 581)
  - Purchasing Dep[artmen]t (Box 581)
  - Rocky Neck State Park (Box 581)
  - Seaside Sanatorium (Box 581)
  - Secretary of [the] State, 4 folders (Box 581)
  - Selective Service (Box 581)
  - Soldiers’, Sailors’, and Marines’ Fund (Box 581)
  - Southbury Training School, 2 folders (Box 581)
  - State Employees (Box 581)
  - State Employees Association, 2 folders (Box 582)
  - State Employees, Conn[ecticut] Association, 2 folders (Box 582)
  - State Employees 40 H[ou]r Work Week, 2 folders (Box 582)
  - State Employees’ Loyalty Oath (Box 582)
  - State Police, Conn[ecticut], 4 folders (Box 582)
  - Tax Department (Box 582)
  - Tax Department (William F. Connelly) [Commissioner], 3 folders (Box 582)
  - Treasurer, 4 folders; half the box (Box 583)
  - Tuberculosis Commission, 2 folders (Box 583)
  - Uncas–on–Thames Sanatorium (Box 583)
  - Undercliff Sanatorium (Box 583)
  - University of Conn[ecticut], 4 folders (Box 583)
  - University of Connecticut, 3 folders (Box 584)
  - University of Connecticut Board of Trustees Agenda, 1954 August 25 (Box 584)
  - Veterans Home & Hospital, Rocky Hill (Box 584)
  - Water Commission, 5 folders (Box 584)
  - Welfare Commissioner, 3 folders (Box 585)
  - Welfare Department (Box 585)
  - Welfare Department Investigation (Box 585)